Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-17. Wages
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. St. Paul, Minnesota, 1953-1954 (Box 551, Folder 11)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Toledo, Ohio, 1953-1955 (Box 551, Folder 12)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Washington, D.C., 1953-1954 (Box 551, Folder 13)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Wage Agreement of March 26, 1954, 1953-1955 (Box 551, Folder 14)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Report of Emergency Board, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 15)
      1954 February 17
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 1, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 16)
      1954 January 6
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 2, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 17)
      1954 January 7
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 3, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 18)
      1954 January 8
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 4, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 19)
      1954 January 11
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 5, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 20)
      1954 January 12
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 6, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 21)
      1954 January 13
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 7, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 22)
      1954 January 14
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 8, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 23)
      1954 January 15
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 9, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 24)
      1954 January 18
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 10, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 25)
      1954 January 19
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Emergency Board Proceedings. Volume 11, 1954 (Box 551, Folder 26)
      1954 January 20
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358, 1953-1954 (Box 551, Folder 27)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Carriers' Exhibits, 1953 (Box 551, Folder 28)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Adjustments of Wage Rates for Railway Express Employees, 1953 (Box 552, Folder 1)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 2)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 3)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 4)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 5)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 6)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 7)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 8)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 9)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 10)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 11)
    - Railway Express Agency, Inc. Case No. A-4358. Transcript of Proceedings, 1954 (Box 552, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-18. Wages
    - Southern Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. C-3525, 1964-1965 (Box 552, Folder 13)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad, 1944-1955 (Box 552, Folder 14)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 552, Folder 15)
    - Southern Pacific Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 552, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-19. Wages
    - Union Pacific Railway, 1949-1955 (Box 552, Folder 17)
    - Union Pacific Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 552, Folder 18)
    - Union Pacific Railway, Lines East. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 552, Folder 19)
    - Union Pacific Railway, Lines West. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 552, Folder 20)
    - Union Pacific Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 552, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 408-20. Wages
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1947-1954 (Box 553, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1960 (Box 553, Folder 2)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5733, 1957-1959 (Box 553, Folder 3)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad. Brotherhood's Ex Parte Submission, 1958 (Box 553, Folder 4)
      1958 August 7
    - Pennsylvania Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 553, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad. Case No. A-2640, 1947-1951 (Box 553, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-21. Wages
    - Great Northern Railroad, 1947-1952 (Box 553, Folder 7)
      September 1947-52.
    - Great Northern Railroad. Ore Docks, Superior, Wisconsin; Lunch Room, Concession, and Station Forces at King Street Station, Seattle, Washington. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 8)
    - Great Northern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 553, Folder 9)
    - Great Northern Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5112, 1956 (Box 553, Folder 10)
    - Great Northern Railroad. Concession Department, King Street Station, Seattle, Washington. Case No. A-4034, 1951-1955 (Box 553, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-22. Wages
    - Northern Pacific Railway, 1947-1951 (Box 553, Folder 12)
    - Northern Pacific Railway, 1953-1957 (Box 553, Folder 13)
    - Northern Pacific Railway. Ore Docks, Superior, Wisconsin; Timber Treating Plants at Brainerd, Minnesota and Paradise, Montana. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 14)
    - Northern Pacific Railway. Ore Docks, Superior, Wisconsin; Timber Treating Plants at Brainerd, Minnesota and Paradise, Montana. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-23. Wages
    - Texas and Pacific Railroad, 1943-1950 (Box 553, Folder 16)
    - Texas and Pacific Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 17)
    - Texas and Pacific Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 18)
    - Texas and Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5026, 1955 (Box 553, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-24. Wages
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad. Centralized Freight Checking System Workers, Schiller Park, Illinois. Mediation Case No. A-5860, 1957-1959 (Box 553, Folder 20)
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad, 1951-1955 (Box 553, Folder 21)
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad, 1947-1950 (Box 553, Folder 22)
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 23)
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul, and Sault Ste. Marie Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-25. Wages
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Lines, 1945-1953 (Box 553, Folder 25)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Lines. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 26)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Lines. Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad Company of Texas; Union Terminal Company, Dallas, Texas: Clerks and Redcaps. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 553, Folder 27)
    - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Lines. Union Terminal Company Seniority Rosters for Clerks, 1953 (Box 553, Folder 28)
      1953 July 1
  - Sub-Series 408-26. Wages
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railroad, 1950-1953 (Box 554, Folder 1)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 2)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railroad, 1955 (Box 554, Folder 3)
    - Nashville, Chattanooga, and St. Louis Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-27. Wages
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railroad, 1947-1953 (Box 554, Folder 5)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 6)
    - St. Louis Southwestern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 554, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-28. Wages
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1961-1964 (Box 554, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 554, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1944-1953 (Box 554, Folder 11)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1954-1960 (Box 554, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-29. Wages
    - Western Pacific Railroad. Western Pacific Medical Department. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 13)
    - Western Pacific Railroad, 1951-1955 (Box 554, Folder 14)
    - Western Pacific Railroad, 1947-1950 (Box 554, Folder 15)
    - Western Pacific Railroad. Western Pacific Medical Department. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 408-30. Wages
    - Reading Railroad Company, 1937-1954 (Box 554, Folder 17)
    - Reading Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1959 (Box 554, Folder 18)
    - Reading Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 408-31. Wages
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad, 1944-1951 (Box 554, Folder 20)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. New York Terminals; Staten Island Rapid Transit; Locust Point Grain Elevator; Camden Warehouses, Inc.; Blue Line Transfer; Baltimore and Ohio Warehouse Company; Terminal Storage Company of Washington, D.C.; Baltimore and Ohio, 1956 (Box 554, Folder 21)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. Curtis Bay Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 22)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad. 40-Hour Week, 1949-1954 (Box 554, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-32. Wages
    - Alton Railroad Company, 1931-1950 (Box 554, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 408-33. Wages
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad, 1932-1951 (Box 554, Folder 25)
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 554, Folder 26)
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 27)
    - Wheeling and Lake Erie Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 408-34. Wages
    - Pere Marquette District, Chesapeake and Ohio Railway, 1946-1955 (Box 554, Folder 29)
    - Pere Marquette District, Chesapeake and Ohio Railway. Manistee and Northeastern District. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 30)
    - Pere Marquette District, Chesapeake and Ohio Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 554, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-35. Wages
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company; St. Louis, San Francisco, and Texas Railway, 1949-1956 (Box 555, Folder 1)
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company; St. Louis, San Francisco, and Texas Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 2)
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company; St. Louis, San Francisco, and Texas Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 3)
    - St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company; St. Louis, San Francisco, and Texas Railway. Mediation Case No. A-5905. Request of Employees for Increase of 15 Cents per Hour for Check Clerks and Centralized Freight Checking System Callers, 1957-1960 (Box 555, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-36. Wages
    - Kansas City Terminal. Clerks and Ushers. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 5)
    - Kansas City Terminal. Clerks and Red Caps. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 6)
    - Kansas City Terminal. Mediation Case No. A-4941, 1955-1956 (Box 555, Folder 7)
    - Kansas City Terminal. Mediation Case No. A-5948. Proposed Reclassification of Hammons, J.N., 1958-1959 (Box 555, Folder 8)
    - Kansas City Terminal. Case No. A-2839, 1947-1956 (Box 555, Folder 9)
    - Kansas City Terminal. Case No. A-4344, 1953-1955 (Box 555, Folder 10)
    - Kansas City Terminal. Case No. A-3298, 1949-1950 (Box 555, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-38. Wages
    - New York Central Railroad, 1947-1952 (Box 555, Folder 12)
    - New York Central Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 13)
    - New York Central Railroad. New York Central Lines East; Cleveland Union Terminals; Grand Central Terminal. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 14)
    - New York Central Railroad. New York Central Lines West, 1956 (Box 555, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-39. Wages
    - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 555, Folder 16)
    - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 17)
    - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 18)
    - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad, 1951-1954 (Box 555, Folder 19)
    - Alabama, Tennessee and Northern Railroad, 1931-1950 (Box 555, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-40. Wages
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company, 1949-1950 (Box 555, Folder 21)
      1949-September 1950.
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 22)
    - Texas and New Orleans Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 408-41. Wages
    - Boston and Albany Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-6411. Proposed Increase of 25 Cents per Hour for Rate Clerks, 1960-1961 (Box 555, Folder 24)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-6376. Proposed Increase in Pay for Engine Dispatchers, 1960-1961 (Box 555, Folder 25)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 26)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 27)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-6316. Proposed Increase of 25 Cents per Hour for Certain Clerical Employees, 1960-1963 (Box 555, Folder 28)
    - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1937-1952 (Box 555, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-42. Wages
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company, 1931-1951 (Box 555, Folder 30)
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 555, Folder 31)
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 32)
    - Minnesota Transfer Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 408-43. Wages
    - Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 34)
    - Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railroad, 1932-1951 (Box 555, Folder 35)
    - Spokane, Portland and Seattle Railroad. Oregon Trunk Railway; Oregon Electric Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 555, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-45. Wages
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad, 1944-1951 (Box 556, Folder 1)
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 556, Folder 2)
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 3)
    - Lehigh and New England Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 408-47. Wages
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railroad, 1946-1952 (Box 556, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, and Omaha Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-48. Wages
    - Norfolk Southern Railroad, 1947-1954 (Box 556, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk Southern Railroad. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 556, Folder 9)
    - Norfolk Southern Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk Southern Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 408-51. Wages
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement -1956 (Box 556, Folder 12)
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement -1955-1956 (Box 556, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-52. Wages
    - St. Paul Union Depot Company. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 556, Folder 14)
    - St. Paul Union Depot Company. Mediation Case No. A-6189, 1960 (Box 556, Folder 15)
    - St. Paul Union Depot Company. Restaurants and Concessions. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 16)
    - St. Paul Union Depot Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-53. Wages
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway, 1946-1951 (Box 556, Folder 18)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway. Railway Transfer Company of the City of Minneapolis. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 19)
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis Railway. Railway Transfer Company of the City of Minneapolis. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 408-54. Wages
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway, 1946-1951 (Box 556, Folder 21)
      1946-October 1951.
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway. Lines West. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 22)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway. Lines East. Clerks and Red Caps. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 23)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway. Clerks and Red Caps. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 556, Folder 24)
    - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul, and Pacific Railway, 1947-1952 (Box 556, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 408-57. Wages
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company. General, 1954-1962 (Box 556, Folder 26)
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company. General, 1944-1953 (Box 556, Folder 27)
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company. General. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 28)
    - Chicago and Northwestern Railway Company. General. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 408-58. Wages
    - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau. General, 1954-1955 (Box 556, Folder 30)
    - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 556, Folder 31)
    - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau, 1945-1953 (Box 556, Folder 32)
    - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 33)
    - Pueblo Joint Interchange Bureau. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 408-59. Wages
    - Washington Terminal Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 35)
    - Washington Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 408-60. Wages
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville Railway Company. General, 1950 (Box 556, Folder 37)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville Railway Company. Mediation Case No. A-4636, 1954 (Box 556, Folder 38)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville Railway Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 39)
    - Chicago, Indianapolis, and Louisville Railway Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 556, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 408-61. Wages
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad. General, 1938-1953 (Box 557, Folder 1)
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 2)
    - Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1956 (Box 557, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 408-62. Wages
    - Erie Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement, 1956-1957 (Box 557, Folder 4)
    - Erie Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement, 1955-1957 (Box 557, Folder 5)
    - Erie Railroad. General, 1949-1954 (Box 557, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 408-64. Wages
    - Duluth, South Shore, and Atlantic Railroad Company. General, 1931-1951 (Box 557, Folder 7)
    - Duluth, South Shore, and Atlantic Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 8)
    - Duluth, South Shore, and Atlantic Railroad Company. Clerical Employees, Ore Dock Employees. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 408-65. Wages
    - Belt Railway of Chicago. General, 1950-1955 (Box 557, Folder 10)
    - Belt Railway of Chicago. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 557, Folder 11)
    - Belt Railway of Chicago. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 12)
    - Belt Railway of Chicago. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 408-66. Wages
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company. General, 1931-1953 (Box 557, Folder 14)
      1931-November 1953.
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 16)
    - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Company. Case No. A-4242, 1953 (Box 557, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 408-67. Wages
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad. General, 1946-1955 (Box 557, Folder 18)
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad. Keokuk, Iowa Union Depot. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 19)
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 20)
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad. Agreement. General Office, Operating, Stores and Mechanical Departments, 1948 (Box 557, Folder 21)
      1948 September 30
    - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad. Aurora, Illinois. Assistant Ticket Agent, Day and Night Ticket Clerks, Ticket Office Employees, 1947-1950 (Box 557, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 408-69. Wages
    - Southern Railway. General, 1949-1956 (Box 557, Folder 23)
    - Southern Railway. Mediation Case No. A-5666. Request for an Upward Adjustment in Existing Rates of Pay of Clerks and Group 5 Employees Working With the So-Called Centralized System of Checking Freight by Use of an Intercommunication System, 1956-1960 (Box 557, Folder 24)
    - Southern Railway. Clerks Case. Puviansky Decided, 1957-1958 (Box 557, Folder 25)
    - Southern Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 26)
    - Southern Railway. Alabama Great Southern Railroad; Cincinnati, New Orleans, and Texas Pacific Railroad; Georgia Southern and Florida Railroad; Harriman and Northeastern Railroad; New Orleans and Northeastern Railroad; New Orleans Terminal Company; St. Joh, 1956 (Box 557, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 408-73. Wages
    - Des Moines Union Railway, 1932-1951 (Box 557, Folder 28)
    - Des Moines Union Railway. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 557, Folder 29)
    - Des Moines Union Railway. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 30)
    - Des Moines Union Railway. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 557, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 408-74. Wages
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. General, 1949-1954 (Box 557, Folder 32)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5842, 1956-1959 (Box 557, Folder 33)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-5845. Pay Increase for Machine Bureau, General Offices, Hamilton Park, Chicago, Illinois, 1957-1960 (Box 558, Folder 1-2)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Agreements. Clerks, Ushers and Red Caps at La Salle Street Station, and Ushers and Red Caps Outside Chicago. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 3)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-4554, 1954-1955 (Box 558, Folder 4)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-4340. Cancellation of Agreement Establishing Step Rates for Inexperienced Clerks in Certain Departments, 1951-1954 (Box 558, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Mediation Case No. A-3818, 1951-1952 (Box 558, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad. Peoria Terminal Company. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 408-75. Wages
    - Union Railway Company of Memphis. General, 1953 (Box 558, Folder 8)
    - Union Railway Company of Memphis. General, 1945-1951 (Box 558, Folder 9)
    - Union Railway Company of Memphis. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1963-1965 (Box 558, Folder 10)
    - Union Railway Company of Memphis. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 11)
    - Union Railway Company of Memphis. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 408-76. Wages
    - Chicago Great Western Railroad. General, 1943-1958 (Box 558, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Great Western Railroad. 1956 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 14)
    - Chicago Great Western Railroad. 1955 Wage Movement (Box 558, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 408-78. Wages